[Applause]
Welcome to Money Management Channel. The
market reached 25,000 points and then corrected again to about
1,000
points.
You saw last Friday again.
So the market has
recovered somewhat. Now, even though the market is at a
costly valuation, there are
still a few companies that are
suitable for quality long-term holdings. Have you
looked at those companies? So,
a few corporate actions, that is,
demergers, have made many announcements like this. Have you looked at a few
companies?
All the demergers have been completed. So, even if we
focus on companies like this, there is
still a lot of opportunity for us to give good returns in the future. As
the market goes upside, there
is a lot of opportunity for corporate action announcements like this.  So
now, let's look at the details of two companies that have completed the corporate actions demerger. Similarly, in
this video, we will discuss the details of two companies that are going to be demerged very soon. First, what we are going to
look at is the complete
companies. If you saw
Reliance IC from the bank,
then a few subsidiary
companies came and demerged. If
you saw Reliance,
then Jio Financial Services
came and demerged. If
you saw IC from the bank, then
Lombard plus Bharat Axe
merged this and introduced a separate company. If
you saw the upcoming hotels,
then they are going to demerge ITC Hotels from ITC. If
you saw Tata Motors coming soon, then
So, Commercial and Messenger are
going to demerge.
All this will be very supportive to take these companies to the next
level.
Now
you see that the company is complete. So,
this is positive for Reliance and Jio Financial Services.
You see,
IC and Bank are also functioning well.
IC and Bank are
performing excellently now.
As for Reliance Industries, we have discussed it in detail.
This is a
stock that is suitable for the long term. We have
analyzed it in detail.
This is a stock that is suitable for the long term.
This is a stock that is suitable for the long term.  We
discussed everything about the stock being offered in a 1:1 ratio. It came to ₹260 and
de-emerged in that range. This company came and
made a slight correction at that time and came from
180 to 210.
So, we can buy this company. We
discussed that way.
Then we discussed in detail
how to buy in this range, level by level, that is, 220, 210, 200.
Now Reliance has come.
Similarly, Jio Finance Services has also
given us good returns. Now,
you have seen Jio Finance Services. If so, it is
trading above 320.
Similarly, Reliance also came with its old bullishness and
broke above 3000. Now, it is
trading at 3000 level.
As for Jio Financial Services, the
problem they had when they first came and separated was that
they did
not have a proper business model, they were
under the Reliance Group, they were just
holding companies,
so they are
taking profit only from the presence of RI, there is no other
income, there has
been a lot of news like that, and now you have seen in the recent
time, they
are implementing all their clear business ideas, they are
introducing a type of black track AMC, and today they are
going to come to the AMC business, insurance
security brokers, Reliance
retail brokers, secured loans,
unsecured loans, everything, you have seen,
so now they are going to introduce all
this, Jio
Financial  There is a lot of opportunity for services to come and
take it to the next level.
After Bajaj Group, there is a big
banking and finance company, so
Jio Financial Services is the one that
is there now. If they come in the market very soon and
give a good tough competition to Bajaj Finance, there
is a lot of opportunity for them to come in the market and give a good tough competition to Bajaj Finance.
You have seen IC Bank,
they have come and taken all the good corporate actions continuously.
Even now, in the recent time, ICCI
Securities came and merged with it.
ICCI, which has a subsidy company, came and became a separate insurance company.
General Insurance came and
separated separately. Then you saw
that Bharat Axe came and
merged with it and introduced ICCI as a separate company.
This is also trading
well in the market now.
General  Insurance companies like IC and
Lambard General Insurance are also performing well.
You have seen these two companies that you have seen now. So, the company whose demerger is complete and the
company that was demerged from it are
performing excellently. You have seen
ITC very soon.
So, ITC Hotels are going to
demerge. You have seen ITC
Hotels too. So, there is a
lot of opportunity to perform well
because as far as hotel
industries and tourism are concerned,
they
are the next big group after the Tata Group. ITC has come and
is performing excellently. In the recent budget, they did not
impose any tax on tobacco.
ITC has been trading at an all-time high since its
announcement of the merger with them. It has
seen a big correction since the 500 level. Why did you see this?
If you don't give shareholders that much
choice, then you
see that there was selling pressure from the stock. So,
this stock reached the 400 level.
Then, recently, it has bounced back
nicely. When it was 500, it reached a
market cap of 6 trillion.
Then, there was a slight correction.
Now, it has come back to the old
level. Now, this company has reached the
510 level. Now, it has
created an all-time high. Now, it is
below 500.  The stock has come and
is trading. As for ITC, they
have announced the merger. They have a lot of opportunities
to complete it in another six months.
So, there is still a lot of
business. There is business. If you look at the
number of
businesses, they have a lot of competition. They have to come and make profits and continue to grow. If they don't have that, they have to upgrade the product. A lot of new investment is needed. They have a number of businesses. They have a competitive business.
So, there are
consumer goods, apples, education, packaging, agribusiness, papermaking
and specialty,
hotel business, IT business,
cigarettes, hotel business. If
you look at the hotel business, they have
40% of ITC holdings.
There is a residual.  They are going to split 60% to the
shareholders. So
you see, in that case, ITC will also
benefit, and similarly, ITC
Hotel will also benefit. As
for Tata Motor, we discussed the details ourselves.
Now, they have delisted all the TVS shares and
Tata
Motor shares will change.
You have seen that, in that case, Tata Motor
shares are going to split Passenger Vehicles and
Commercial Vehicles separately.
All the ratios for this have been announced. As for
Tata Motor, so far,
two types of shares have come and are
being traded. There are DVR shares
separately and there are ordinary shares. The main difference between the
two is the voting
rights.
Tata Motor has 10 shares in DVR,
so you have
seven in Tata Motor.  They are going to give shares.
On the other hand, in the case of Tata Motors, there
is a possibility of splitting into three sectors, that is,
commercial vehicles and passenger
vehicles are being separated separately. If there is no such thing, there is a
finance company, that is, Tata
Motor Finance Company, and
Tata Capital also
has a lot of opportunities to merge. So, if the beloved
Tata Motors comes and performs
well and excels in commercial and passenger vehicles, there is a
lot of opportunities to improve.
Now,
in the case of Tata Motors, it is trading above ₹1000.
all the stocks we discuss have come and in the short term, even if we
make a return, we should
hold these companies for a long run of 5 to 10 years.
Then, we can create an excellent win.
As for our channel,
50% of the people who subscribe to our channel and
watch it, 50% of
the people who don't subscribe, please subscribe to our channel and
support us.
Our channel member community will
update the portfolio, that is,
what stocks I bought and what
stocks I sold, what changes I made in my portfolio. I will
share information about this. I will
post until the daily market update is finished.
What events are there in the corporate world? We will
share some useful information about our Indian economy.
Join the number community and follow this regularly.
Then you will improve your knowledge.  Not
only that, but it will also be
supportive in every way to build your portfolio healthily. I think
all the information discussed here will be useful for you. If
this video was useful for you, then
come and
subscribe to our channel, like our video,
share it, the comment section
is open, so
what is your opinion about this video, what are the doubts in it,
post it in the comment section, then it will
be a good support not only for you but also for all our viewers. I am not a SEBI registered
advisor. If you
come and watch all the videos posted on our channel, please note that the
videos posted for educational or informational purposes are
definitely risky investments,
so you should discuss them with your financial
advisor.  No, you make your own
decision and invest.